okay first I'd like you to follow follow
your breath
um
slightly
but not two times
[Music]
keep your hands soft
push back your shoulders
stay very aware of the exhales
now another exhale I'd like you to
Exhale
from your right nostril
so that's the beginning of the breath
at the start of your breath you exhale
from the right nostril
video
we've been fine so I'd like it to take
30 breaths
right nostril
no
30 breaths by one of your nostrils is
blocked
imagine breathe
[Music]
but just imagine exhaling
from your right nostril
s
[Music]
these are
um
tightens really
push out a second
more conscious exhale from the right
nostril
but okay it's okay
either
woman
personally I like to keep my thirsty
even though my eyes
so my eyes are looking
when you're watching your breath
good evening
[Music]
now I'd like you to think of one
interaction you had yesterday or this
morning
if you didn't meet anyone yesterday you
know back there
[Music]
foreign
then I'd like you to recall
why did you meet them what what were you
meeting them for why did you meet the
other person
what were you hoping
to achieve maybe it was just a few
minutes talk
catch up with them or
yeah
[Music]
online
and then I'd like you to think about why
did they meet with you what were they
trying to get out of interacting with
you
when they
spoke to you
hello
[Music]
foreign
how did they see you if if you put
yourself
in their body yeah
[Music]
I don't mean your parents
the way you were acting
acting the way you were speaking
knowing the feeling that God about how
you were thinking about them again okay
kind were you how thoughtful were you in
the interaction how did the
how did you feel to them
goodbye
foreign
[Music]
and then please come back to your breath
goodbye
[Music]
and inhale through the left
on the horizon even though your eyes are
sick
[Music]
foreign
keep drinking okay
you guys were supposed to meditate
yesterday about
um
[Music]
we would like to share how it felt or
anything though
what emotions
where you tend to feel the same emotion
for your boss
yeah okay
um I love this one this is amazing
just because I felt like yeah
like I just personally but
professionally just are so remarkable
when we're a team
um
[Music]
help
them I guess
you know when they were looking at I
guess me
I'm not
sorry
more of a state of service like mentally
like how can I take away something off
their place in order to sort of have the
bigger picture of being successful and
so in each case I found myself
kind of looking at like
as a person
um
and the boss were slightly different and
the colleagues sense I was how can I
take a little bit off of their plate
and the bosses sense the feeling was
more like
in order
I don't know it was almost like um
just relax a little bit you know like I
found myself trying to sort of like how
do I and that's just not trying so hard
with the boss I guess
um
lower one for example
how can I sort of help them how can I
see the world
from their point of view and maybe make
them realize
it was really beautiful I just enjoyed
it
by the way when you're translating
it's extremely difficult
[Music]
so I'm just that's a
that's something you might want to try
when you're meditating on it or when
you're describing it
loud
every time you breathe pause
like four years
since the first time that I've done this
meditations
[Music]
get a job
so the emotion was
jealousy
foreign
[Music]
I felt
games
[Music]
stay in that state all day
help them feel safe
in my presence
to go on what I'm looking at right
thank you
I don't know I think it's a very
good but um
can you hear me okay
a little louder okay okay
I looked back at me
I saw an arrogant person
jealousy
okay so
um
[Music]
these wonderful teachings um
thanks my boss is unqualified
well and he believes that I think he's
qualified
when I put myself
but then when I put myself
like I'm nice to
but I kind of also don't think so should
I think he's qualified when I kind of
don't think he's qualified
you're not talking about me right
now
in Manhattan and um
there's this feeling when you're in a
group
that if everyone agrees with you
know what I mean
someone else to agree with you
[Music]
in the more true it is that your opinion
is true but then
I mean technically everyone can be wrong
just because more people support them
that's correct
there's a tendency
but I think your question is
if you really do believe they're
incompetent
to get support from
I think it's that
put yourself in there
from this week
that's what you want
options
of innovation innovation in a company
you can detect a fake diamond out of a
hundred dollars
no one ever used it before for that yeah
so that's a technical uh Innovation but
I think mostly Innovations means
[Music]
express my real opinion and then what
you've done is you've set yourself up
for a dichotomy or two choices yes or no
and I think a great leader and a great
employee
solution which makes sense
negotiation
[Music]
it's not
um
to never fire somebody
the first one was hard
but uh
because Christmas is 60 of the time
so you work you build up the point of
course
because there's no nobody buys diamond
rings in January
so I'm not saying
to lose money and ruin a company
if there's someone who's acting up
[Music]
it's not a Buddhist thing to
keep an incompetent bosses hurting
everybody
that that's not a Buddhist practice
but a Buddhist practice would be to find
them a good job that's even more
interesting for them